Subtitled by
It's time to go.
All of Us
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
The world's a power!
Thing is, I got beef with
the world government.
Apparently they're not
just killing Stella.
They're gonna kill me too!
So rude, am I right?
Am I right? Hey! Say it's rude! Correct.
It's very rude. You paused!
But anyways, I got a plan
to turn this thing around.
So...
Your job is to help Mama kill some
people who are annoying her, okay?
I shut the frontier dome, so
I want everyone in here dead.
Except me, Stella, and
the hostages underground.
Say roger if you got all that.
Roger!
Sweetness, now when you start
kicking their butts, Problem is,
the punks will go, wait,
who's ordering these things?
And then they'll catch me.
I can't beat them in a fair fight.
So I need a backup plan.
Cue a snake. Yes?
You gotta petrify me.
And do it in front of them, all right?
Right.
Then come back and undo
it when no one's looking.
Roger.
Hmm.
Oh, before I forget, there's a couple
places in the lab you shouldn't blow up.
This is important.
So listen real carefully.
Ready, steady, cut!
Everyone on the ship, quick!
We need to get Omega now!
Everyone ready?
Let's get to work.
Okay, Pirate!
Only a fool would oppose our Chief.
You're gonna die today.
I told you!
No, not the wrong thing!
Get lost or broke, Gribbis!
Nah, what he said!
Pops, you're ditchers!
Help me out with you fools!
I do not like you!
Look, you will never reach, chief.
Go away!
No!
I shall be cross with you.
You are so brave, princess.
Is Red Hair mocking us?
These can't be his real allies.
How do these clowns even
survive the new world?
I get what you mean, but he's
got a few famous names in there.
Don't get sloppy.
Whether they're weak or strong,
I'm not here to show mercy.
Are we ready to set sail hey boss the
other crews went out to stop kid then tell
them to retreat i don't want them dying
for nothing whoa whoa whoa wait wait wait
come on chief what are
you trying to pull i think
i should be asking you
that we'll handle this?
They won't lay a damn finger on you!
That's right!
Thanks, guys.
For the offer, I mean.
But seriously, stay put.
David, get off me! Just leave me!
Please don't go!
At least let us fight beside you!
Whoa, that's enough. Easy.
Aw, come on!
You can't be taken off already!
Yeah, you just got here!
We've hardly had a chance to chat!
We got places to be.
I was just stopping
here for a quick drink.
I'm sorry, but let me go, guys. Come on.
A big shot showed up because
I bummed around too long.
All right, one more time.
Tell the ships to retreat.
You know I'd take you, but I can't
be seen with a bunch of weaklings.
Tell us how you really feel!
Well, it doesn't matter if we're weak.
We're invincible as long
as we have your flag.
Don't get too comfortable, Ollie.
My flag can't scare off old age for you.
Do you hear the way he talks to me?
No respect for his elders.
Hurry up, boss.
Your fans can wait. Oh, please.
Yeah, we'll wrap this up in
two shakes of a drumstick.
Don't worry.
Don't get cocky.
Kids worth three billion, you know.
They grow up fast these days.
You gotta be careful.
Thought they had a hell
of a fight in Wano.
Does it look like their
wounds have healed?
Uh-huh.
They're in tip-top shape.
Definitely ready for a fight.
That's good to hear.
What about Blackbeard?
Any updates yet?
No.
All we know is that he left Pirate Island.
I was so sure he'd show
up in the land of Wano.
On go.
Ready.
Here's your intel on kit.
We're so proud of you turning
your homework in on time.
That's enough.
We got a ship to load.
I see.
So he's from the South Blue.
And it looks like he's
gone on quite the rampage.
How many ships are there? Nine total.
There's some faces I've
seen on wanted posters.
I don't care who we're up against.
Let them come.
I'll wipe them all out in second place.
Here it comes. Yes.
He's pulling the ship! Do something!
What is that?
A cannon?
I'll track you under my feet.
I'm going straight to the top, and
I won't let anyone get in my way!
See you in hell!
Come on, Red Hair!
The next one's for you!
Damn it.
Tell the fleet to spread out!
You see something, boss?
Dory! Froggy! Get ready!
We were born ready!
Hard to port!
Too much power!
He'll kill them!
I guess he saw a future he didn't like.
See you in hell!
Should have expected this.
You kept me waiting!
Divine Departure.
Oh, my God.
Partner yeah won't be
long now that's right
Just look at how far we've come only one
road poneglyph left to take then we set
Sail for the one piece you hear that Kaido
big mom red hair ah all the old timers
couldn't cut it They can't keep up with us
our crews made it to the front of the pack
i will be king of the pirates No one can
stop me killer you
bastard you laughing at me
Oh!
Oh! God, do it! Kid!
Boss, wake up!
Open your eyes, please!
Get out! Dammit!
The killer got hurt trying to protect him!
No!
Stop, Red Hair! We surrender.
Please have mercy.
We're begging you.
Please don't kill our boss.
Go, Emma. Bring them out.
Hurry!
These are road photoglyphs.
All the ones we've got.
You can have them.
Just please let us live.
Come on, Chief! Time to go!
Let's go!
Hey, you guys!
Look over there!
It's not over!
Something's coming!
Hey, little ones!
You know what happens when you point
a gun at someone's home, right?
You better be ready for
them to start shooting back!
HATOKO!
Thus,
the battle at Elbaf ended,
used as Captain Kidd,
with a bounty of three billion berries,
fell alongside his crew.
It was a massacre.
My promise is that I'm in
the middle of the heart.
Everyone, I don't have a dream.
I'm just holding one hand.
Thank you.